Every time the rain no longer falls, and I
see the sky, I think the rain is falling.
Back to when I was a child.
Who could only cry?
Blindly chasing after him.
I fell far behind my only thought.
One day I will be stronger.
Bridery and gratitude.
Fading with the wind.
Am I stronger now than I was before?
Or as weak as back then?
I don't know for sure.
But until I do, my voyage will not end.
No matter what's next, I'm
walking straight ahead.
So let's go, there's nothing
that can stop us now.
Though time's all on our side,
we'll never let it pull us down.
And we may fall, but we'll
always keep on standing.
There's no way anything
will take what I hope.
The voices inside me push
me to keep surviving.
I'll go on, I'll get through,
no matter what I gotta do.
The fiercest storms of
all can pour upon me.
I don't care why in the
world would I turn back?
So let's go,
there's nothing that can stop.
The tides that are on our side
will never let it pull us down.
And we may fall, but we'll
always keep on standing.
There's no way anything will take
what I hold dear away from me.
I know the future's there for us to see.
This Marine Ford business
is gonna change the world!
So it's true after all!
The news spread like wildfire falling on
ears that could scarcely believe the words.
Ace, son of the great gold Roger, fell
in battle alongside Whitebeard. Extra!
Get ready to issue an extra!
We just received some breaking news.
Whitebeard was killed
shortly after Firefist Ace,
and the Marines have claimed victory.
He's really dead.
Yeah!
This crew is done for!
There's peace again!
If the Navy can take care of Whitebeard!
Then the rest of the pirates will follow!
While many celebrated,
those who saw these events unfold
with their own eyes stand transfixed,
their mouths agape,?
words frozen on their lips.
Bon voyage, Whitebeard.
His name was Edward Newgate.
In his prime, he stood against
even the king of the pirates.
His crew was his family.
And he fought beside them
into the ripe old age of 72.
The world knew him as Whitebeard.
He had stepped boldly into
Marineford and brought
the walls of the Navy
headquarters down around him.
And yet, despite his superhuman efforts,
the Navy forces, aided
by the Seven Warlords,
proved too strong?
Ah, what a day!
It's the birth of a new world,
or the death of an old one I think today's
party may have some life in it yet.
That bastard!
Marco, for what it's worth,
we all share your sentiment.
But it's not the time for revenge.
Yeah, I get it. Let's go.
Save your tears and hurry up, you fools.
You haven't forgotten your
captain's final orders, have you?
No distractions.
We'll be setting sail
as quickly as we can.
Understood.
That old Carter was tough as nails.
I thought he'd never die.
A minor delay, yes, but
scarcely unexpected.
Now for the fun part.
Yeah, let's give them a magic
show they'll never forget!
Be careful, who knows
what they're planning!
You monster!
Haven't you done enough to Pops?
Watch carefully, it's a good trick!
So good, in fact, it's gonna shake
the whole world down to its core!
Whatever this is, it's not good.
Is he doing something to
Whitebeard's corpse in there?
Now, now.
I know you're curious, but
please don't interrupt.
Don't get too cocky, pirates!
He joined the seven warlords
just so he could betray us.
Whatever he's up to, you
can bet it won't be good.
I can't wait.
So what happens if this plan
doesn't work? We disband.
Hey!
Hey, where are you going?
Captain!
Where do you think, stupid?
Someplace far away from here!
My plan to kill Whitebeard
is shot, obviously!
So we're running away?
I was so close!
Yeah, I'm scared! I admit it!
I'd rather dig a hole, crawl in,
and live the rest of my measurable
life in there than face this guy!
I don't care if you think
I'm pathetic, dammit!
I don't need you losers around anyway!
Captain Buggy! He's crying.
Is it our fault? Aha!
He's teaching us a lesson about sympathy.
Seeing Whitebeard
suffering filled him with
pity and humanity triumphed over savagery.
Beautiful!
His message is engraved upon my soul,
but he laughed, fearing
we wouldn't understand.
He had a shot at fame and fortune,
but he understood that the cost of his
personal integrity was
a price too high to pay.
Because material gains
are ultimately meaningless
and public acclaim is fleeting
in these trying times.
I've seen the light, Captain.
It's as if I've been reborn.
Share more of your wisdom with us.
I'm scared for knowledge. Go away.
Keep moving.
We're almost there.
Luffy I know it hurts right now but you
must carry on for in a world without
ace your courage will be needed tomorrow
and every day after fire it's a heavy
weight but one I'm confident you can bear
Jinbei I know I might not make it out
of this alive I'm sorry but if I die
would you look after
are my brother for me.
I fear you misjudge my character, Ace.
I mean no disrespect, but I may
not be as charitable as you think.
I'm certain you care for your brother,
but we live in a world of pirates.
I offer my aid to those
I hold in high regard?
but only to them.
We've got room on this ship over here!
Coming!
What the?
Damn it!
And we were so close, too!
You mean we're stuck?
Well, we've gotta do something!
Aokiji's coming!
Somebody stop him!
We have to run! Go!
Did you really think you
could get away from me?
Why don't you save yourself some
trouble and let me kill you?
Hand over dragons, son, and
I may decide to spare you.
Akainu, I thought Pops killed him.
But how did he survive the fall?
Did he come out of the ground?
His lava powers freak me out.
Team bane a generous offer,
but I must refuse you
aren't the only tenacious
one here I've decided to protect this boy.
No matter the cost have it your way then.
I won't ask twice
You're not gonna lay a
finger on Straw Hat pops
wanted us to protect him
useless cowards out of my way
through Empire Faceproof Synthesis!
If I may, I believe I can
be of assistance here.
Great Scissors!
Keep those magma-covered paws
of yours off of Straw Boy!
This kid is history, and
his father will be next!
Hell-wing-ga!
He's been pushing
himself since Impel Down.
He's passed his limit
physically and emotionally.
It's a wonder he's still alive.
One more hiccup and we could lose him.
If something were to happen on my watch,
I could never show my giant
face to his father again.
As Dragon's comrade, it's my
duty to protect his family.
I feel the same.
You think you're hot stuff?
You ain't seen nothing yet, Magma Boy.
Why?
Because this queen is on fire!
Ladies and gentlemen, mostly gentlemen,
we are grateful for your patience.
Captain Teach and his merry men
present to you a stunning spectacle,
the likes of which you've never seen.
One, two... Daddy!
What did he do?
He was doing something in there, but what?
The Whitebeard's body looks the same.
Blackbeard's too, I think.
It's been fun.
Huh?
The Warlord thing, I mean.
You played your part well.
But as you'll see I
don't need you anymore!
This one here you all know it's my
dark dark fruit power, but this?
Just watch!
No, it can't be!
An earthquake?
That's the power of the
Tremor Tremor fruit!
I thought if you had two
telephone powers you would die,
and how did you take them for
Whitebeard in the first place?
I can't believe you pulled it off!
He stole that power from Pops!
I know, but how?
That isn't normal, is it?
A hand of darkness to call forth the void.
A hand of light to shake the
heavens and rend the earth.
Both are mine.
And the world will tremble
with my every step.
Only a fool would dare defy me.
I don't know how he did it, but he did it.
You can't fake having a power like that.
But does he know that we don't? Damn!
Young, we beat Whitebeard, but so what?
It's even worse than before! But hold on.
I thought if you tried to get
a second Devil Fruit power,
then your body would, like, blow up.
Yeah, for normal people,
that's how it works.
But you know as well as I do
that teaches anything but normal.
And with that body of his, he can pull
a trick we couldn't even dream of.
He's probably been planning
this thing for ages now.
Got your attention now, Z!
This is a wake-up call to all the boring
peace-lovers, the half-assed pirates,
the fat-headed fools in world
government, the ignorant masses.
This is a nightmare.
It just has to be.
We all must answer to the hand of fate.
And fate has chosen me
to conquer this world.
H-Seal's coming down!
Run for it!
Abandon your balls!
We're all gonna die!
It's over.
There's nothing left.
The pirates, they took everything we had.
Our citadel where we've watched
over these waters for centuries.
It's all crumbling down the
symbol of the Navy's strength.
This is a nightmare
Damn he planned this from
the very start didn't he?
He betrayed Whitebeard, captured
Ace, and became a warlord.
All the force them into this battle!
Alright then, take a good luck, cuz you
ain't seen nothing like this before?
They can't stop him now.
No one can.
I can hardly blame them.
I'd be crying too if my
enemies had this kind of power.
Now what?
Took some time, but this
is a hell of a payoff.
I got the whole world wrapped
around my finger you bastard
Hey, what's wrong?
You don't want to fight?
I'm right here
If you let me get away
who knows what I might do?
Okay, I warned ya
Now where to start?
Oh, I know
How about I give
Marineford a burial at sea?
He wouldn't dare!
Sarkwave!
You can tear down our buildings,
but in time we will rebuild them.
But this island is different.
It's more than a symbol of our strength.
It stands in the center of the world.
Admiral.
And that means if we
want to protect innocent
people from criminals such as yourself,
it must be our stronghold, so
its light can reach every corner.
Compassion is justice.
It defies chaos.
It doesn't perish, and it will
certainly not sink by your hand.
Turn to learn your place.
Well that's a downright noble
sentiment, compassion or what have you.
Well, come on!
Let's see what you're made of.
That isn't good.
We bought you some time.
Get him out of here.
Good luck.
Oh, no!
Bad move, Chop.
Now get over here.
You're a pesky one, aren't you?
Nu-kama-ken-po, aesthetic technique.
This one's my fat suctioning fist.
I like it hot, baby!
This isn't a game dammit get the
hell out of my way or pay the price
Who's next?
Don't you dare, Akaido!
You'd be wise to run while you
can, I have no business with you!
I dare not face him on dry
land, but the sea will aid me!
The water, it's frozen solid!
Damn, Aokiji!
Here he comes!
Nowhere left to run, you bloated fish!
I'm helpless then!
Hand him over!
I'm putting an end to this!
It looks like it went
straight through him it might
have been Straw Hat and
they're falling fast too
Still have some fight left in you.
That's a pity
Forgive me, Luffy.
It seems that I couldn't uphold my vow.
You might have saved yourself instead
of condemning the both of you.
If you keep making me miss,
it won't be good for anyone.
A blow to the heart would
be quick and painless.
Better than this.
The boy's got a hole in his chest You
sure you still want to protect him?
You know he's gonna die either way.
I refuse to let him perish.
He protected us.
They won't be up there long.
So catch them when they fall
and put them on our ship!
Why the sudden change of heart?
I say if you're going to protect
someone then do it right!
I don't like either of you, but if you
screw this up, then you'll let the Navy win!
Sorry, I blew it, guys!
You had so much faith in me, but I was
nothing more than a coward all along!
I'll just float away somewhere
and find a hole to crawl in,
because the only thing I'm
the king of is to survive it!
Oh crap, you're getting away!
They're stuck in here?
Wait, what's happening here?
Nice catch, Captain Page!
You saved Straw Hat and Jimmy!
I never should have doubted you!
He wasn't running!
He was just looking out for Straw Hat!
Because all the glory in the world means
nothing compared to the
life of an old friend!
How beautiful!
His heart's as pure as a baby lamb! Huh?
I can't hear what they're
saying, but I bet it's stupid.
Huh? Jinbei?
And Straw Hat?
What the hell?
What are you idiots doing
all the way up here,
and why are you both covered in blood?
This is weird, even for you guys.
Also, is it just me, or is it hot?
Ah!
That's Madmon!
Thank you, my red-nosed friend.
You saved our lives.
We're not friends.
I don't even know what's
going on right now.
I'm afraid I allowed Luffy to be harmed.
We must find a doctor.
He was burned quite badly.
I don't care!
And good luck finding a doctor
in the middle of this mess.
I had to trump the both of you right now.
Wait, were you making fun of my nose?
How many people do I have to
go through to finish that brat?
Rolls Rundle!
You're fools, each and every one of you.
Is one boy so damned important that
you're willing to throw your lives away?
You may mock us if you please,
but there is a strength
in Straw Hat's tenacity
that may prove invaluable to this world.
Pop spent his life on him.
He has to carry on Ace's legacy.
This is the dawn of a new era, and
we have a duty to see him through it.
Noble sentiment from a bunch of criminals,
but in the end, it's just empty talk.
I won't hesitate to strike you down.
Same here.
Your insistence on killing Straw Hat
just proves to us how much you fear him.
And if a tough guy like you
is scared of a boy like him,
that means he's worth protecting.
To the death, if need be!
Uh, can't you jackasses do
anything without my help?
Hey, are you even listening to me?
You didn't just pass out, did you?
Hey, I didn't need it, buddy.
Don't die on me.
Come on, you gotta tell me where to go.
I'm lost here. Help!
Frankly, I should be applauding
him for making Straw Hat suffer.
But I suppose the pirate in me
would rather punch him in the face.
I see that trying to reason
with you is a lost cause.
Have it your way.
This is too much.
It's Sengoku versus Blackbeard over there.
And it's Aka-Inu versus the
commanders on that side.
I thought this war was
supposed to be over.
Captain Buggy, do something, anything.
I've got my hands full, okay?
What is that?
It was underwater.
A ship?
It's a submarine.
That's a Charlie Roger.
Huh?
I don't take orders from you, pal.
And besides, what do you want
with him anyway, you weirdo?
Actually, who the hell are you?
Straw Hat may be my enemy someday, but
I'll let the fates decide that one.
Either way, it'd be a
waste to let him die here.
Hand him over and we can escape.
He'll die without my help! What?
Trust me, I'm a doctor